<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>Dope-T-Rope | Technically Dope</title>
        <description>Dope-T-Rope is a ambitious Project Found For Sharing Tech News and Upda ...</description>
        <link>https://dopetrope.tk/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://dopetrope.tk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 18:34:54 +0530</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 18:34:54 +0530</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v3.8.7</generator>
        
        <item>
            <title>Instagram makes it easier to see when you’re broadcasting music you can’t use</title>
            <description>To help protect against accidental copyright infringement</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Instagram has posted its guidelines for using copyrighted music during live videos, Stories, and other posts on the platform, and part of the announcement includes a new update to the notification that pops up to tell users they’re using unlicensed art in ways that violate its rules. The changes to the pop-up notification are designed around helping users avoid Instagram’s automated interruptions — like muting or outright blocking — that occurs if a piece of licensed music plays for too long over or in the background of a live video.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, the notification pops up earlier in live broadcasts to...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 08:21:56 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/instagram-makes-it-easier-to-see-when-you-re-broadcasting-music-you-can-t-use/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/instagram-makes-it-easier-to-see-when-you-re-broadcasting-music-you-can-t-use/</guid>
            <category>facebook</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Twitter brings its new quote tweet view to Android and the web</title>
            <description>The new view arrived on iOS last week</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;witter made it easier to see quote tweets on iOS on May 12th, and that new functionality is now available on Twitter for Android and for the web, the company announced today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you tap or click on the “Retweets” word on a tweet, you’ll be taken to a new page that lets you look at one of two columns: a column showing retweets with comments and a column showing all retweets without comments. You can see how it works in the video below:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;There’s now more to the conversation behind the Retweet count. On iOS, tapping...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 08:15:05 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/twitter-brings-its-new-quote-tweet-view-to-android-and-the-web/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/twitter-brings-its-new-quote-tweet-view-to-android-and-the-web/</guid>
            <category>tech-knowledge</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Netflix is making it easier for people to cancel their subscriptions</title>
            <description>Memberships can collect dust</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Netflix is trying to make it easier for people to cancel their service with a new automated prompt that will ask subscribers if they want to continue paying after a lengthy period of inactivity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On May 18th, the company started reaching out to subscribers who haven’t used the service in two years (or within one year of their initial sign-up for newer customers) to let them know they can either keep their membership or have it canceled upon the next billing cycle. Those customers represent a small number of Netflix’s overall 183 million subscriber base, totaling less than half of...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 08:13:19 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/netflix-is-making-it-easier-for-people-to-cancel-their-subscriptions/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/netflix-is-making-it-easier-for-people-to-cancel-their-subscriptions/</guid>
            <category>tech-knowledge</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>MICROSOFT’S NEW FLUID OFFICE DOCUMENT IS GOOGLE DOCS ON STEROIDS</title>
            <description>Fluid is coming to Office.com and going open source</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft is creating a new kind of Office document. Instead of Word, Excel, or PowerPoint, the company has created Lego blocks of Office content that live on the web. The tables, graphs, and lists that you typically find in Office documents are transforming into living, collaborative modules that exist outside of traditional documents.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Microsoft calls its Lego blocks Fluid components, and they can be edited in real time by anyone in any app. The idea is that you could create things like a table without having to switch to multiple apps to get it done, and the table will persist...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 08:02:18 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/microsoft-s-new-fluid-office-document-is-google-docs-on-steroids/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/microsoft-s-new-fluid-office-document-is-google-docs-on-steroids/</guid>
            <category>tech-knowledge</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google Play Movies adds its first Dolby Vision HDR titles</title>
            <description>Today, we’re seeing a batch of Dolby Vision HDR titles available on the platform.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Google announced support for HDR content on Google Play Movies &amp;amp; TV. The company specifically mentioned HDR10+, but we knew it was preparing to support Dolby Vision HDR as well. Today, we’re seeing a batch of Dolby Vision HDR titles available on the platform.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Joker and A Simple Favor are the first two Dolby Vision HDR titles on Google Play Movies. It appears that Google is preparing to announce official support as there is a “Top Dolby Vision movies” section when you search for “Dolby.” Play Movies is still well behind other platforms when it comes to...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 07:51:58 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-play-movies-adds-its-first-dolby-vision-hdr-titles/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-play-movies-adds-its-first-dolby-vision-hdr-titles/</guid>
            <category>google</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google releases Assistant-powered Action Blocks</title>
            <description>new accessibility features in Maps, Live Transcribe, and Sound Amplifier</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Today is Global Accessibility Awareness Day and Google is using the opportunity to announce several new accessibility-minded features. “Action Blocks” are finally ready for a public release, and new accessibility features are coming to Live Transcribe, Sound Amplifier, and Google Maps.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h5 id=&quot;action-blocks&quot;&gt;Action Blocks&lt;/h5&gt; &lt;p&gt;Action Blocks is a feature that Google introduced last year. In a nutshell, it’s an app that allows you to create buttons on the home screen to perform Google Assistant commands. The idea is these buttons are much easier for people with some form of cognitive disability use, rather than interacting with their voice or text.&lt;/p&gt;...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 07:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-releases-assistant-powered-action-blocks/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-releases-assistant-powered-action-blocks/</guid>
            <category>google</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Microsoft releases Terminal 1.0 and Windows Package Manager</title>
            <description>Microsoft had announced Windows Terminal.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft holds a conference event every year for software engineers and web developers. Called Build, or //build/, the event is a conference for developers that primarily work on Windows, Microsoft Azure, and other technologies. While Microsoft holds an event on the ground every year, as they have in the past years, but because of COVID-19, Build 2020 is an online-only announcement. On the occasion, Microsoft has announced a plethora of new features, such as Windows Terminal 1.0, Windows Package Manager, Windows Subsystem for Linux 2, all of which will be useful to a lot of developers in some form or...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:19:07 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/microsoft-releases-terminal-1-0-and-windows-package-manager-announces-linux-gui-app-support-and-gpu-acceleration-for-wsl-2/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/microsoft-releases-terminal-1-0-and-windows-package-manager-announces-linux-gui-app-support-and-gpu-acceleration-for-wsl-2/</guid>
            <category>tech-knowledge</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Digital Wellbeing prepares to track your sleep, let you take Night Notes, and more</title>
            <description>New “Daily Device Usage” toggle in “Manage Your Data”</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;oogle first unveiled Digital Wellbeing at Google I/O 2018 with a handful of tools to help users reduce their smartphone usage, but the company has steadily improved upon the app in the last 2 years by introducing loads of new features. In the latest beta update to version 1.0.312292882, Google is preparing to introduce major new features to help you get a better night’s sleep.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h6 id=&quot;new-daily-device-usage-toggle-in-manage-your-data&quot;&gt;New “Daily Device Usage” toggle in “Manage Your Data”&lt;/h6&gt; &lt;p&gt;The first feature that Google is introducing is already available for everyone on the latest beta release. If you open the settings menu in Digital...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:11:42 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/digital-wellbeing-prepares-to-track-your-sleep-let-you-take-night-notes-and-more/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/digital-wellbeing-prepares-to-track-your-sleep-let-you-take-night-notes-and-more/</guid>
            <category>android</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>YouTube Music player page adds a “Related” tab for recommended songs and playlists</title>
            <description>Related tab lists down recommended songs and playlists based on whatever you’re currently listening to</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year in March, Google rolled out a redesigned player page for YouTube Music on Android. The updated UI included a new tab for static lyrics at the bottom of the music player, alongside the Up Next tab which lists all songs in the current playlist. Now, according to a couple of recent posts on Reddit, YouTube Music is getting a new “Related” tab in the same position on the player page.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.xda-developers.com/files/2020/05/YouTube-Music-Related-tab-975x1024.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Youtube Music&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As its name suggests, the Related tab lists down recommended songs and playlists based on whatever you’re currently listening to. As you...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:04:18 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/youtube-music-player-page-adds-a-related-tab-for-recommended-songs-and-playlists/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/youtube-music-player-page-adds-a-related-tab-for-recommended-songs-and-playlists/</guid>
            <category>youtube</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Blog is Live After Months of Rebuilding</title>
            <description>Promise you to keep this Blog constantly Updated</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;h5 id=&quot;hey-there-this-is-shan-from-dopetrope&quot;&gt;Hey there, This is Shan from &lt;em&gt;Dopetrope&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/h5&gt; &lt;p&gt;This Website has Been Upgraded with Massive Features in the Backend for Faster Loading of Website with Some Cool Asynchronous Programming.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now Has a Faster CDN for Images and Videos Posted Here.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Everything in this Website has Been Completely Automated. Our Website now Has its Own API for Interaction with Multiple Web / Android Apps.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Therefore in Future, You May be Able to use this as a Android App. Everything is Possible with the help of the API that is Constructed in the Backend.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;enjoy-faster-content-posts&quot;&gt;Enjoy Faster Content / Posts&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;h5 id=&quot;from-shantksudharshan-tk&quot;&gt;from...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 17:45:41 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/blog-is-live-after-months-of-rebuilding/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/blog-is-live-after-months-of-rebuilding/</guid>
            <category>blog</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Welcome to Read Write Tech V2.0 (Now Dope-T-Rope)</title>
            <description>Website's Upgraded with Nice Cool New Features</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;h4 id=&quot;read-write-tech-is-now-dope-t-rope---dopetech&quot;&gt;Read Write Tech is Now Dope-T-Rope - #DopeTech&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;See the &lt;a href=&quot;https://dopetrope.tk/&quot;&gt;Website Here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h5 id=&quot;what-is-it&quot;&gt;What is it?&lt;/h5&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dope-T-Rope is a Personal Tech Blog / News Website that Gets You Updated with Latest Techno News.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h5 id=&quot;features&quot;&gt;Features&lt;/h5&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#live-search&quot;&gt;Live Search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#estimated-reading-time&quot;&gt;Estimated Reading Time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#reading-progress-bar&quot;&gt;Reading Progress Bar&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(optional)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#new-post-tag&quot;&gt;“New Post” tag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#load-images-on-demand&quot;&gt;Load images on demand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#push-menu&quot;&gt;Push Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#svg-icons&quot;&gt;SVG icons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#shell-script-to-create-posts&quot;&gt;Shell script to create posts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#tags-page&quot;&gt;Tags page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#about-page&quot;&gt;About page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#contact-page&quot;&gt;Contact page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#404-error-page&quot;&gt;404 error page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#feed-rss&quot;&gt;Feed RSS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#disqus&quot;&gt;Disqus&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(optional)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#featured-post&quot;&gt;Featured post&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(optional)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thiagorossener/jekflix-template/wiki/Features#home-page-pagination&quot;&gt;Home page pagination&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(optional)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 03:40:58 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/Welcome-v2/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/Welcome-v2/</guid>
            <category>blog</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Interactive ‘dynamic email’ rolling out to Gmail for Android and iOS</title>
            <description>Google wants the future of email to be less static and more interactive</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Google wants the future of email to be less static and more interactive. Its solution based on Accelerated Mobile Pages has found industry support, and “dynamic email” is now coming to Gmail for Android and iOS.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instead of clicking links that open in a browser, dynamic emails let you interact with calendar invites, respond to questionnaires, and browse catalogs right from a message. One particularly interesting use case is commenting in a Google Docs thread right from the email notification already in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This saves you from having to open the full app and lets you quickly return to...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 16:10:58 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/interactive-dynamic-email-rolling-out-to-gmail-for-android-and-ios/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/interactive-dynamic-email-rolling-out-to-gmail-for-android-and-ios/</guid>
            <category>android</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Motorola revives the Razr as an Android Foldable, $1,500 Verizon exclusive</title>
            <description>The Motorola Razr is likely the most iconic flip phone ever released.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The Motorola Razr is likely the most iconic flip phone ever released. In 2011, Motorola and Verizon tried to revive the brand with a series of thin — for their time — Android phones. The Lenovo-owned company is now bringing back the Razr as an Android Foldable.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The 2019 Razr offers much more compelling hardware that harkens to its namesake. When closed, it keeps the original look of the flip phone, albeit wider. In clamshell mode, there is an outer 2.7-inch 800 x 600 “Quick View” screen that notes networking and battery status up top, followed by the time, date...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 21:34:26 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/motorola-revives-the-razr-as-an-android-foldable-1-500-verizon-exclusive/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/motorola-revives-the-razr-as-an-android-foldable-1-500-verizon-exclusive/</guid>
            <category>motorola</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Apple Music ‘Replay’ feature lets you see most played songs, albums, much more</title>
            <description>As first reported by TechCrunch, the new Replay feature provides users a playlist of their most listened to songs from 2019, as well as prior years dating all the way back to 2015.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Apple is taking a page out of Spotify’s book and adding a new year-in-review feature to Apple Music. Starting today, you can access your Apple Music “Replay” playlist through Apple Music on the web and in the Music apps on iOS, iPadOS, and Mac.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As first reported by TechCrunch, the new Replay feature provides users a playlist of their most listened to songs from 2019, as well as prior years dating all the way back to 2015.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can also see interesting insights into your most popular artists, albums, and more. For the Apple Music Replay playlists, you can share...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 19:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/apple-music-replay-feature-lets-you-see-most-played-songs-albums-much-more/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/apple-music-replay-feature-lets-you-see-most-played-songs-albums-much-more/</guid>
            <category>apple</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>YouTube Music begins rolling out Discover Mix playlist</title>
            <description>The latest that’s beginning to roll out is called the Discover Mix.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, YouTube Music has relied on playlists from the service’s curators to automated creations based on your listening history. The latest that’s beginning to roll out is called the “Discover Mix.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Last month, Google added a new “Released” playlist to compete with Apple Music’s “New Music Daily” and Spotify’s “New Music Friday.” The “Discover Mix” is very similar in concept to the latter service’s very popular “Discover Weekly.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The cover art uses the full YouTube logo — instead of Music’s round icon — in the top-left corner and has a very neon aesthetic of an abstract and bright...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 15:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/youtube-music-begins-rolling-out-discover-mix-playlist/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/youtube-music-begins-rolling-out-discover-mix-playlist/</guid>
            <category>google</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google launches YouTube Music Charts in India</title>
            <description>YouTube’s first dedicated external signal highlighting videos</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Views on YouTube are a huge pop culture metric that define popularity and success. Google today is launching YouTube Music Charts in India, thus “closing a critical gap.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;India has long been one of the most unique and vibrant music markets in the world. Nowhere is that more visible than on YouTube. We look forward to celebrating the success of the artists, songs and music videos that are resonating with Indian music fans.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;YouTube’s Music Charts track artists, songs, music videos, and what’s trending. The video company in May brought localized rankings to 44 countries worldwide. Top songs,...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 14:42:26 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-launches-youtube-music-charts-in-india/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-launches-youtube-music-charts-in-india/</guid>
            <category>youtube</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google Photos Introduces New Instagram-Like Stories Feature</title>
            <description>Google is rolling out new features to its Photos app today</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Google is rolling out new features to its Photos app today, including the ability to order same-day prints (not available in India) and a new photo slideshow feature in Instagram Stories style called Memories.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Now, it’s easier than ever to relive your best moments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rolling out today, you can take a stroll down memory lane right from Google Photos with our new Memories feature. See the highlights from this week over the years. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/FBtRk2DTQe&quot;&gt;https://t.co/FBtRk2DTQe&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/vG1A210vOg&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/vG1A210vOg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Google Photos (@googlephotos) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/googlephotos/status/1172198993499045889?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;September 12, 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;Starting today, every time you hop...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 13:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-photos-introduces-new-instagram-like-stories-feature/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-photos-introduces-new-instagram-like-stories-feature/</guid>
            <category>google</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google app 10.61 Insight</title>
            <description>Google app 10.61 preps ‘Smart Screenshots’ with Lens</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Google app 10.61 is rolling out as the latest beta and reveals work on a new “Smart Screenshots” feature that integrates Lens. A bug with the “Preferred input” setting for Assistant has also been resolved.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About APK Insight:&lt;/strong&gt; In this ‘APK Insight’ post, we’ve decompiled the latest version of an application that Google uploaded to the Play Store. When we decompile these files (called APKs, in the case of Android apps), we’re able to see various lines of code within that hint at possible future features. Keep in mind that Google may or may not ever ship these features, and...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 18:30:41 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-app-10-61-insight/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-app-10-61-insight/</guid>
            <category>app-insights</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google Assistant testing denser suggestions UI on Android</title>
            <description>Google is experimenting with a new UI for the Google Assistant’s suggested actions</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;As we’ve seen in recent Pixel 4 leaks, Google has a number of design changes in mind in the near future for the Google Assistant on Pixel phones. For those of us who won’t be getting the “next-generation” Assistant right away, Google is also testing out a new UI for its proactive suggestions on Android.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As it stands today, when you invoke the Google Assistant on Android, you’re presented with the typical voice UI and a number of suggested actions contained in pill-shaped “chips.” While they flow nicely with the Material Design spec, these chips are not particularly good for...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 11:30:16 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-assistant-testing-denser-suggestions-ui-on-android/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-assistant-testing-denser-suggestions-ui-on-android/</guid>
            <category>apps-updates</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Here are a bunch of other Pixel 4 pictures that corroborate previous leaks</title>
            <description>At this point, there’s really not much we don’t know about the Pixel 4. </description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The Pixel 4 has leaked so many times this month that we’re getting tired of the early looks, but now another huge gallery of pictures has hit the web which further corroborates other leaks and reports about the device.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At this point, there’s really not much we don’t know about the Pixel 4. Many of the details about the device we previously exclusively reported on such as the 90Hz display, 128GB of storage, and more are confirmed in a gallery of over 20 images that were sent to The Verge. Notably, the device pictured if apparently “not a final unit.”&lt;/p&gt;...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 10:53:48 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/here-are-a-bunch-of-other-pixel-4-pictures-that-corroborate-previous-leaks/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/here-are-a-bunch-of-other-pixel-4-pictures-that-corroborate-previous-leaks/</guid>
            <category>google</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google app and Assistant dark theme start rolling out</title>
            <description>A dark theme for Google Assistant and Search is now beginning to roll out for some users.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;With the launch of Android 10 last week, Google teased night-friendly looks for Gmail and Maps. A dark theme for Google Assistant and Search is now beginning to roll out for some users.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We’ve been tracking development on a dark mode for the Google app, which incorporates Assistant, since April. Limited testing began in June and a wider launch might now be underway. There are several reports on Pixel and Samsung devices with both Search and Assistant adopting it simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Google Discover adopts a dark theme that is similar to what’s long been at the left of the Pixel Launcher....</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 07:25:19 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-app-and-assistant-dark-theme-start-rolling-out/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-app-and-assistant-dark-theme-start-rolling-out/</guid>
            <category>apps-updates</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>This Bengaluru Techie Has Designed An Air-Conditioned Helmet To Keep You Cool While Riding</title>
            <description>Nobody likes to wear helmets!</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Nobody likes to wear helmets! Unless, you’re a bike-enthusiast who takes pride flaunting his riding essentials, helmets are a pain. They’re heavy and suffocating even though they save lives. Besides, the new traffic rules have got people fussing about having to wear a helmet on sunny days. That’s another level of discomfort altogether. But, a man has now devised a very ingenious hack to solve all your riding woes!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sandeep Dahiya, director at a multinational company, has developed a prototype model of an air-conditioned helmet that can keep you cool while riding under the scorching sun. Passionate about designing user-friendly...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 07:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/this-bengaluru-techie-has-designed-an-air-conditioned-helmet-to-keep-you-cool-while-riding/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/this-bengaluru-techie-has-designed-an-air-conditioned-helmet-to-keep-you-cool-while-riding/</guid>
            <category>tech-research</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Gmail for Android dark theme begins rolling out [Gallery]</title>
            <description>Dark theme is now rolling out to Gmail for Android today via a sever-side update.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Following Android 10’s public launch last week, many users have been waiting for all of Google’s apps to offer darker looks. After a brief tease on Android.com, a dark theme is now rolling out to Gmail for Android today via a sever-side update.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Like other Google apps in recent months, there are three options in Gmail: Light, Dark, and System default. The dark theme is quite straightforward with the email client adopting a dark gray for the background and navigation drawer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In that latter part of the UI, a red accent color is still leveraged to note what inbox you’re...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 19:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/gmail-for-android-dark-theme-begins-rolling-out-gallery/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/gmail-for-android-dark-theme-begins-rolling-out-gallery/</guid>
            <category>apps-updates</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google Search will now highlight and elevate original reporting</title>
            <description>This will see articles that broke a story — instead of reblogs — be prominently featured to people searching and stay visible longer.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Google’s latest news initiative has Search “elevating original reporting.” This will see articles that broke a story — instead of reblogs — be prominently featured to people searching and stay visible longer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to Google, this is meant to account for how “original reporting on a subject doesn’t always stay in the spotlight for long” in today’s “fast-paced world of news.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Many news articles, investigations, exclusive interviews, or other work can be so notable that they generate interest and follow-up coverage from other publications. And in other cases, many stories cover a single news development, with all of them...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 19:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-search-will-now-highlight-and-elevate-original-reporting/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-search-will-now-highlight-and-elevate-original-reporting/</guid>
            <category>google</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Here’s everything Apple didn’t announce at its September iPhone 11 event</title>
            <description>There are a number of product launches that Apple has decided to save for a potential October event</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Apple’s September event brought us the iPhone 11, iPhone 11 Pro, and iPhone 11 Pro Max, Apple Watch Series 5, launch details for Apple Arcade and Apple TV+, and even the new seventh-generation iPad with a larger 10.2-inch screen. However, there are a number of product launches that Apple has decided to save for a potential October event (or another time) and some that were possibly even scrapped from the September event at the last minute. Read on for a look at everything Apple didn’t announce at Steve Jobs Theater in September but could unveil soon.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some of the upcoming...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 11:24:01 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/here-s-everything-apple-didn-t-announce-at-its-september-iphone-11-event/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/here-s-everything-apple-didn-t-announce-at-its-september-iphone-11-event/</guid>
            <category>apple</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Google Translate 6.2</title>
            <description>Fixes ‘Tap to Translate’ on Android 10, preps ‘Continuous Translation’</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;During the Android Q Betas, Google Translate’s “Tap to Translate” did not work. Following Android 10’s launch last week, a new version of the app fixes the feature and makes it more subtle. Meanwhile, version 6.2 hints at a continuously audio translation mode.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About APK Insight:&lt;/strong&gt; In this ‘APK Insight’ post, we’ve decompiled the latest version of an application that Google uploaded to the Play Store. When we decompile these files (called APKs, in the case of Android apps), we’re able to see various lines of code within that hint at possible future features. Keep in mind that Google may...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 11:18:07 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/google-translate-6-2/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/google-translate-6-2/</guid>
            <category>app-insights</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Chrome 77 for Android rolling out</title>
            <description>New Downloads page, ‘Send this page’ sharing</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Following the Mac, Windows, and Linux release, Chrome 77 for Android is now rolling out. There are tweaks to the Downloads page and wider availability of “Send this page” sharing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Chrome already allows you to check what tabs are open on devices signed in with your Google Account. Version 77 is adding a direct “Send this page” feature that can be accessed from the system share sheet. While the “Send to your devices” target with the Chrome icon might appear when using Chrome Custom Tabs, sending only works in the browser.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tapping slides up a “Send to” list of all...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 10:54:40 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/chrome-77-for-android-rolling-out/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/chrome-77-for-android-rolling-out/</guid>
            <category>app-insights</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Here’s what the Google Play Store’s in-app review system will look like</title>
            <description>Google Play Store could soon be providing a way for app developers to get reviews from their users</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Back in July, XDA-Developers discovered that the Google Play Store could soon be providing a way for app developers to get reviews from their users without ever needing to leave the app. Today, we’ve uncovered a demo showing exactly how this in-app review process will work for Play Store apps.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About APK Insight: In this ‘APK Insight’ post, we’ve decompiled the latest version of an application that Google uploaded to the Play Store. When we decompile these files (called APKs, in the case of Android apps), we’re able to see various lines of code within that hint at possible future...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 10:31:46 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/here-s-what-the-google-play-store-s-in-app-review-system-will-look-like/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/here-s-what-the-google-play-store-s-in-app-review-system-will-look-like/</guid>
            <category>app-insights</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Here’s everything Apple announced during its iPhone 11 keynote today</title>
            <description>The event included new iPhone announcements, details on future Services, and much more.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;After months of speculation, Apple today officially held its “By innovation only” iPhone 11 and Apple Watch Series 5 event at Steve Jobs Theater. The event included new iPhone announcements, details on future Services, and much more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Read on as we recap everything Apple announced today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apple Arcade and Apple TV+&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Apple kicked things off today by offering an update on two of its upcoming Services: Apple Arcade and Apple TV+. First off, Apple Arcade is Apple’s upcoming game subscription service offered on iOS, macOS, and tvOS.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Apple confirmed today that is launching Apple Arcade on September 19, and that...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 12:46:22 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/here-s-everything-apple-announced-during-its-iphone-11-keynote-today/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/here-s-everything-apple-announced-during-its-iphone-11-keynote-today/</guid>
            <category>apple</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Hands-on with the iPhone 11, iPhone 11 Pro, and Apple Watch Series 5 [Videos]</title>
            <description>Head below for a roundup of early hands-on videos with the iPhone 11, iPhone 11 Pro, iPhone 11 Pro Max, and Apple Watch Series 5.</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;After Apple unveiled the iPhone 11, iPhone 11 Pro, and Apple Watch Series 5 at Steve Jobs Theater, members of the press were given time to go hands-on with the company’s latest products.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head below for a roundup of early hands-on videos with the iPhone 11, iPhone 11 Pro, iPhone 11 Pro Max, and Apple Watch Series 5.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Apple Watch Series 5 is the first Apple Watch to feature an always-on display. The new always-on display works by intelligently dimming the screen when a user’s wrist is down and returns to full brightness with a...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 11:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://dopetrope.tk/hands-on-with-the-iphone-11-iphone-11-pro-and-apple-watch-series-5-videos/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dopetrope.tk/hands-on-with-the-iphone-11-iphone-11-pro-and-apple-watch-series-5-videos/</guid>
            <category>apple</category>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>

